Diane Wolkstein collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 3: Story Performances
  - Subseries 3: Audio and Video
    - Monkey King, September 28, 2009
      - Rehearsal 2 - DVD, afc2016057_dc136; 7 video files (IFO, VOB, BUP)
      - Rehearsal 3 - VHS, AFC 2016/057: MV264; 1 videocassette (VHS)
      - Rehearsal 3 - VHS, AFC 2016/057: MV265; 1 videocassette (VHS)
      - Rehearsal 3 - DVD, afc2016057_dc135; 7 video files (IFO, VOB, BUP)
    - Monkey King, October 7, 2009
      - Part A2 - VHS, AFC 2016/057: MV242; 1 videocassette (VHS)
      - Part A2 - DVD, afc2016057_dc149; 7 video files (IFO, VOB, BUP)
      - Part A3 - VHS, AFC 2016/057: MV243; 1 videocassette (VHS)
      - Part A3 - DVD, afc2016057_dc150; 10 video files (IFO, VOB, BUP)
    - Monkey King, October 23, 2009
      - Columbia Prep, AFC 2016/057: MV252; 1 videocassette (VHS)
      - Rehearsal - VHS, AFC 2016/057: MV268; 1 videocassette (VHS)
      - Rehearsal - DVD, afc2016057_dc366; 14 video files (IFO, VOB, BUP)
    - Monkey King, October 29, 2009
      - Musician Angle 1, AFC 2016/057: MV272; 1 videocassette (VHS)
      - Musician Angle 2, AFC 2016/057: MV288; 1 videocassette (VHS-C)
    - Monkey King, October 30, 2009
      - Part 1 - VHS, AFC 2016/057: MV230; 1 videocassette (VHS)
      - Part 1 - VHS, AFC 2016/057: MV256; 1 videocassette (VHS)
      - Part 2 - VHS, AFC 2016/057: MV232; 1 videocassette (VHS)
      - Part 2 - VHS, AFC 2016/057: MV257; 1 videocassette (VHS)
      - DVD version, afc2016057_dc376; 14 video files (IFO, VOB, BUP)
      - Work in Progress 1 - VHS, AFC 2016/057: MV269; 1 videocassette (VHS)
      - Work in Progress 2 - VHS, AFC 2016/057: MV270; 1 videocassette (VHS)
      - Work in Progress Q&A - VHS, AFC 2016/057: MV271; 1 videocassette (VHS)
    - Monkey King, November 2009
      - Performance, afc2016057_dc340; 14 video files (IFO, VOB, BUP)
      - Q&A, afc2016057_dc376; 8 video files (IFO, VOB, BUP)
    - Monkey King, December 2, 2009
      - Part A1 - VHS, AFC 2016/057: MV240; 1 videocassette (VHS)
      - Part A1 - VHS, AFC 2016/057: MV239; 1 videocassette (VHS)
      - Part A2 - VHS, AFC 2016/057: MV241; 1 videocassette (VHS)
      - Part A3 - VHS, AFC 2016/057: MV244; 1 videocassette (VHS)
      - DVD version, afc2016057_dc131; 7 video files (IFO, VOB, BUP)
    - Monkey King, December 11, 2009
      - Part B1 - VHS, AFC 2016/057: MV245; 1 videocassette (VHS)
      - Part B1 - VHS, AFC 2016/057: MV246; 1 videocassette (VHS)
      - Part B1 - DVD, afc2016057_dc134; 7 video files (IFO, VOB, BUP)
      - Part B2 - VHS, AFC 2016/057: MV247; 1 videocassette (VHS)
      - Part B2 - DVD, afc2016057_dc133; 8 video files (IFO, VOB, BUP)
      - Part B2A - VHS, AFC 2016/057: MV248; 1 videocassette (VHS)
      - Part B2B - VHS, AFC 2016/057: MV249; 1 videocassette (VHS)
      - Part B3 - VHS, AFC 2016/057: MV250; 1 videocassette (VHS)
      - Part B3 - VHS, AFC 2016/057: MV251; 1 videocassette (VHS)
      - Part B3 - DVD, afc2016057_dc132; 5 video files (IFO, VOB, BUP)
    - Monkey King, 2009
      - Part 1, afc2016057_dc368; 10 video files (IFO, VOB, BUP)
      - Part 2, afc2016057_dc369; Marathon; 10 video files (IFO, VOB, BUP)
      - Part 3, afc2016057_dc370; Marathon 2; 8 video files (IFO, VOB, BUP)
      - Part 4, afc2016057_dc371; No sound rehearsal; 9 video files (IFO, VOB, BUP)
      - Part 5, afc2016057_dc367; 11 video files (IFO, VOB, BUP)
    - Monkey King, 2009
      - Part 1, AFC 2016/057: MV229; 1 videocassette (VHS)
      - Part 2, AFC 2016/057: MV231; 1 videocassette (VHS)
      - Part 3, AFC 2016/057: MV234; 1 videocassette (VHS)
      - Part 4, AFC 2016/057: MV236; 1 videocassette (VHS)
      - Part 5, AFC 2016/057: MV237; 1 videocassette (VHS)
      - Part 6, AFC 2016/057: MV238; 1 videocassette (VHS)
    - Monkey King, September 2010, afc2016057_dc327; Loft show; 11 video files (IFO, VOB, BUP)
    - Monkey King, circa 2011, afc2016057_dc333; Performed at Village Community School; 3 video files (MP4); 9 color photographs (JPG)
    - Monkey King, April 1, 2011, afc2016057_dc330; Performed at NYU; 14 video files (IFO, VOB, BUP)
    - Monkey King, June 4, 2011, afc2016057_dc345; Performed at Rothko Chapel with Jeff Greene; 9 video files (IFO, VOB, BUP)
    - Monkey King, May 2012, afc2016057_dc353; Performed at the Asian Art Museum; 6 video files (IFO, VOB, BUP)
    - Monkey King, August 31, 2012, afc2016057_dc364; Performed at Singapore International Storytelling Festival; 9 video files (IFO, VOB, BUP)
    - Monkey King, undated, AFC 2016/057: MV255; Disc 2, Tape 1; 1 videocassette (VHS)
    - Monkey King, undated, AFC 2016/057: MV267; Rehearsal NYC; 1 videocassette (VHS)
    - Monkey King, undated, AFC 2016/057: SR208; Tape II; 1 sound cassette
    - Monkey King, undated, afc2016057_dc354; 7 video files (IFO, VOB, BUP)
    - Monkey King, undated, afc2016057_dc380; 10 video files (IFO, VOB, BUP)
    - The Nearly Invincible Monkey King, February 2, 2011, afc2016057_dc078; Performed with Jeff Greene at the Fairfax Theater.; 9 video files (IFO, VOB, BUP)
    - Monkey Transfer Tales, March 5, 1991, AFC 2016/057: MV289; 1 videocassette (VHS-C)
    - Most Incredible Thing of All, Sun Mother, June 5, 2004, Performed in Central Park
      - Hi8 version, AFC 2016/057: MV290; 1 videocassette (Hi8)
      - DVD version, afc2016057_dc111; 8 video files (IFO, VOB, BUP)
    - Mouse Tales; Elsie Piddock Skips in Her Sleep, June 27, 1998, AFC 2016/057: SR209; 1 sound cassette
    - Side A: Mouse Tales; Side B: The Knee-High Man, undated, AFC 2016/057: SR210; 1 sound cassette
    - Mr. Gumpy, Ma Was a Pirate, undated, AFC 2016/057: SR211; 1 sound cassette
    - National Storytelling Festival, Seer of Lublin's Shirt, 1982, AFC 2016/057: SR231; 1 sound cassette
    - National Storytelling Festival, undated, AFC 2016/057: SR212; 1 sound cassette
    - National Storytelling Festival, undated, AFC 2016/057: SR245; 1 sound cassette
    - Ocean Visits Sun and Moon, undated, AFC 2016/057: SR213; 1 sound cassette
    - Old Rinkrank, circa 2007, afc2016057_dc254; Performed at Hans Christian Andersen statue; 7 video files (IFO, VOB, BUP)
    - Old Rinkrank, Oom Razoom, circa 1980s, AFC 2016/057: MV291; 1 videocassette (Hi8)
    - Oom Razoom, circa 1991-1993
      - Hi8 version, AFC 2016/057: MV292; 1 videocassette (Hi8)
      - Part 1 - Hi8, AFC 2016/057: MV293; 1 videocassette (Hi8)
      - Part 2 - Hi8, AFC 2016/057: MV294; 1 videocassette (Hi8)
    - Oom Razoom, 1993, afc2016057_dc081; Performed at the C.G. Jung 25th Retrospective; Shirley Keller; 10 video files (IFO, VOB, BUP)
    - Once Upon a Story, September 1971, AFC 2016/057: MV295; 1 videocassette (Hi8)
    - Once Upon a Time with Diane Wolkstein: 3 Stories and an Interview, undated
      - MiniDV version, AFC 2016/057: MV015; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
      - Hi8 version, AFC 2016/057: MV296; 1 videocassette (Hi8)
    - Orange Tree Vocals, Owl Vocals, undated, AFC 2016/057: SR214; 1 sound cassette (DAT)
    - Osiris, undated, AFC 2016/057: MV297; 1 videocassette (Hi8)
    - Ossian, The Last of the Fianna, undated, AFC 2016/057: SR215; 1 sound cassette
    - Performance at Met, Diane's First Opera, April 1, 2009, AFC 2016/057: MV298; 1 videocassette (Hi8)
    - Pie songs, undated, AFC 2016/057: SR216; 1 sound cassette
    - Pirate Mother, Mouse Tales, Cool Ride, Hot Balloons, undated, AFC 2016/057: SR217; 1 sound cassette
    - The Princess in Transition with Jean Feraca, Wisconsin Public Radio, August 25, 1999, AFC 2016/057: SR218; 1 sound cassette
    - Psyche and Eros, November 22, 1983, AFC 2016/057: SR220; 1 sound cassette
    - Psyche and Eros, March 15, 1984, AFC 2016/057: SR221; 1 sound cassette
    - Psyche and Eros, October 22, 1985, AFC 2016/057: SR222; 1 sound cassette
    - Psyche and Eros, April 10, 1986, AFC 2016/057: SR223; 1 sound cassette
    - Psyche and Eros, September 16, 1986, AFC 2016/057: SR224; 1 sound cassette
    - Psyche and Eros, June 18, 1994, AFC 2016/057: SR225; 1 sound cassette
    - Psyche and Eros, undated, AFC 2016/057: SR226; 1 sound cassette
    - Qi Gong, undated, AFC 2016/057: MV299; 1 videocassette (Hi8)
    - Rehearsal tape, 1970-1971, AFC 2016/057: SR227; 1 sound cassette
    - Rifle County Library, October 16, 1997, AFC 2016/057: MV300; 1 videocassette (Hi8)
    - Romping, undated, AFC 2016/057: SR228; 1 sound cassette (DAT)
    - Romping, undated, AFC 2016/057: SR229; 1 sound cassette
    - Russian Fairytale, May 18, 1988, AFC 2016/057: SR230; 1 sound cassette
    - Ruth, November 23, 2003, Diane Wolkstein performs the Story of Ruth with Michael Braudy and Ken Yamazaki at Tellabration! 2003.
      - Hi8 version, AFC 2016/057: MV302; 1 videocassette (Hi8)
      - DVD version, afc2016057_dc101; 7 video files (IFO, VOB, BUP)
    - Ruth, September 29, 2006, AFC 2016/057: MV303; 1 videocassette (Hi8)
    - Ruth, January 2007, afc2016057_dc046; Performed in Austin, Texas.; 7 video files (IFO, VOB, BUP)
    - Ruth, undated, AFC 2016/057: MV301; 1 videocassette (Hi8)
    - Sacred Stories Central Park, June 6, 2009, AFC 2016/057: MV304; 1 videocassette (Hi8)
    - Santa Teresa Anna's class, February 23, 1994, AFC 2016/057: MV306; 1 videocassette (Hi8)
    - Santa Teresa Anna's class, March 2, 1995, AFC 2016/057: MV305; 1 videocassette (Hi8)
    - School of Lebanon Road storytelling performance, circa 1980s, afc2016057_dc103; Diane Wolkstein performs Glass Mountain and Bouki Dances the Kokioko at School of Lebanon Road, New Hampshire.; 7 video files (IFO, VOB, BUP)
    - Shiva and Sati, Jonesborough National Storytelling Festival, No. 25, October 4, 1997
      - DVD version, afc2016057_dc019; 6 video files (IFO, VOB, BUP)
      - VHS version, AFC 2016/057: MV222; 1 videocassette (VHS)
      - CD version, afc2016057_dc037; 2 sound files (WAV)
    - Silly Sally rehearsal, undated, AFC 2016/057: SR232; 1 sound cassette
    - Sleepy Hollow, 1987, AFC 2016/057: SR233; 1 sound cassette
    - Song of Songs, April 10, 1986
      - Sound cassette version, AFC 2016/057: SR234; 1 sound cassette
      - Sound cassette version, AFC 2016/057: SR235; 1 sound cassette
    - Song of Songs, April 11, 1991, AFC 2016/057: SR236; 1 sound cassette
    - Song of Songs, undated, AFC 2016/057: SR237; 1 sound cassette
    - Song of Songs, undated, AFC 2016/057: SR238; 1 sound cassette
    - Song of Songs, undated, AFC 2016/057: MV307; 1 videocassette (Hi8)
    - Songs, undated, AFC 2016/057: SR239; 1 sound cassette
    - Songs - Mouse's Painting and others, undated, AFC 2016/057: SR240; 1 sound cassette
    - Spirit Horse story-telling band, undated, AFC 2016/057: SR241; 1 sound cassette
    - Stories, October 20, 1997, AFC 2016/057: SR242; 1 sound cassette
    - Stories, undated, AFC 2016/057: SR243; 1 sound cassette
    - Storyteller, July 7, 1993, AFC 2016/057: MV312; 1 videocassette (Hi8)
    - Storyteller, undated, AFC 2016/057: MV310; 1 videocassette (Hi8)
    - Storyteller, undated, AFC 2016/057: MV311; 1 videocassette (Hi8)
    - Storyteller, undated, AFC 2016/057: MV313; 1 videocassette (Hi8)
    - Storytelling #2, February 10, 1984, AFC 2016/057: MV315; 1 videocassette (Hi8)
    - Storytelling, June 5, 1993, AFC 2016/057: MV314; 1 videocassette (Hi8)
    - Storytelling at New York Library, March 9, 1983, AFC 2016/057: SR246; 1 sound cassette
    - Storytelling at Provincetown Playhouse, April 4, 2004, AFC 2016/057: SR219; 1 sound cassette
    - Storytelling at Provincetown Playhouse, October 8, 2006, AFC 2016/057: MV317; 1 videocassette (Hi8)
    - Storytime Show #129, undated, AFC 2016/057: MV320; 1 videocassette (Hi8)
    - Tales of the Heart, May 5, 1981
      - Parts 1 and 2, AFC 2016/057: SR251; 1 sound cassette
      - Part 3, AFC 2016/057: SR252; 1 sound cassette
    - Tales of the Heart, undated, AFC 2016/057: SR247; 1 sound cassette
    - Tales of the Heart, undated, AFC 2016/057: SR248; 1 sound cassette
    - Tales of the Heart, undated, AFC 2016/057: SR249; 1 sound cassette
    - Tales of the Heart, undated, AFC 2016/057: SR250; 1 sound cassette
    - Teach Me to Make Lace, undated, AFC 2016/057: SR253; 1 sound cassette
    - Side A: Three B'rer Rabbit Stories; Side B: The Legend of Scarface, undated, AFC 2016/057: SR254; 1 sound cassette
    - Timponogos Storytelling Festival, Once Upon a Time.. .Highlights, 1997, afc2016057_dc079; Parts 1 and 2; 9 video files (IFO, VOB, BUP)
    - Topsy Turvy Stories, March 12, 2000, AFC 2016/057: SR258; 1 sound cassette
    - Topsy Turvy Stories, undated, AFC 2016/057: SR259; 1 sound cassette
    - Treasures of the Heart, October 28, 2003
      - Part 1 - video tape, AFC 2016/057: MV335; 1 video tape: 1/2" open reel
      - Part 2 - video tape, AFC 2016/057: MV336; 1 video tape: 1/2" open reel
      - DVD version, afc2016057_dc020; Performed at Cedar Crest. Accompanied by Shirley Keller.; Shirley Keller; 9 video files (IFO, VOB, BUP)
    - Trickster Stories, March 18, 1995, AFC 2016/057: SR260; 1 sound cassette
    - Trickster Stories, April 1, 1995
      - Part 1, AFC 2016/057: SR261; 1 sound cassette
      - Part 2, AFC 2016/057: SR262; 1 sound cassette
    - Trickster Stories, Monkey King beginning, undated, AFC 2016/057: SR263; 1 sound cassette
    - Tristan and Iseult, 1987
      - Video tape version, AFC 2016/057: MV337; 1 video tape: 1/2" open reel
      - DVD version, afc2016057_dc116; At the C.G. Jung Foundation, New York City; 9 video files (IFO, VOB, BUP)
    - Tristan and Iseult, January 28, 1989, AFC 2016/057: SR264; 1 sound cassette
    - Tristan and Iseult, February 3, 1989
      - Sound cassette version, AFC 2016/057: SR265; 1 sound cassette
      - Part 1 - sound cassette, AFC 2016/057: SR267; 1 sound cassette
      - Part 2 - sound cassette, AFC 2016/057: SR268; 1 sound cassette
    - Tristan and Iseult, undated, AFC 2016/057: SR266; 1 sound cassette
    - Ugly Duckling, Elsie Piddock, November 11, 1991, AFC 2016/057: MV340; 1 film reel (16mm)
    - Side A: United States: 3 Rootabaga Stories; Side B: Wee Red Man, undated, AFC 2016/057: SR269; 1 sound cassette
    - [Unlabeled stories]
      - DW_CK_INT_06509_01, undated, AFC 2016/057: MV078; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
      - DW_CPK_TLA_065PT09_01, undated, AFC 2016/057: MV079; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
      - DW_NJG_SHK_06510_01, undated, AFC 2016/057: MV080; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
      - DW_NJG_SHK_06510_02, undated, AFC 2016/057: MV081; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
      - DW_NJG_TLA_06510_01, undated, AFC 2016/057: MV082; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
      - DW_NJG_TLA_06510_02, undated, AFC 2016/057: MV083; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
    - [Unlabeled story]
      - Part 1, undated, AFC 2016/057: MV016; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
      - Part 2, undated, AFC 2016/057: MV017; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
    - [Unlabeled], undated, AFC 2016/057: MV341; 1 videocassette (MiniDV)
    - [Unlabeled], undated, AFC 2016/057: MV342; 1 video tape: 1/2" open reel
    - Vegetable Soup #37, October 15, 1975, AFC 2016/057: MV343; 1 videocassette (VHS)
    - White Wave, circa 1980s, AFC 2016/057: MV345; 1 videocassette (VHS)
    - Writer's Live, March 20, 1998, AFC 2016/057: MV346; 1 videocassette (VHS)
    - Yang Yang Flying in the Sky, undated, AFC 2016/057: SR270; 1 sound cassette
- Series 4: WNYC Stories From Many Lands Radio Show
  Interview transcripts, programs, and audio recordings of Stories from Many Lands, produced and hosted by Diane Wolkstein, which aired on WNYC radio from 1968 to 1980.
  - Subseries 1: Manuscripts and Photographic Prints
    - Storytelling interviews schedule, 1979, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 11/6)
    - Baker, Augusta interview, undated, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 11/7)
    - Belpre, Pura interview, undated, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 11/8)
    - Bodger, Joan interview, undated, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 11/9)
    - Cantaback, Rabbi Shlomo interview, undated, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 11/10)
    - Courlander, Harold interview, 1974, 1 folder of manuscript materials with 1 black-and-white photographic print (Box-folder 11/11)
    - Dodge, Marshall interview, undated, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 11/12)
    - Klein, Barbra interview, undated, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 11/13)
    - McLendon, Sally interview, undated, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 11/14)
    - Singer, Isaac Bashevis interview, 1974, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 11/15)
    - Smith, Jimmy Neil interview, undated, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 11/16)
    - Sutton-Smith, Brian interview, undated, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 11/17)
    - Timpanelli, Joyce interview, undated, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 11/18)
    - WNYC portfolio, 1967-1973, 1 folder of manuscript materials with 2 black-and-white photographic prints and 1 color photographic print (Box-folder 18/11)
    - WNYC portfolio, 1973-1977, 1 folder of manuscript materials with 2 color photographic prints (Box-folder 11/19)
    - WNYC portfolio, 1978-1980, 1 folder of manuscript materials with 2 black-and-white photographic prints (Box-folder 12/1)
    - WNYC radio photographs, undated, 6 black-and-white contact sheets and 8 black-and-white photographic prints (Box-folder 12/2)
    - WNYC radio show list, undated, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 12/3)
    - WNYC storytelling festival, 1979, 1 folder of manuscript materials (Box-folder 18/12)
  - Subseries 2: Audio and Video
    Arranged and described according to the numbering system used by Diane Wolkstein. This subseries is incomplete, not all of the episodes from Wolkstein's WNYC show are represented.
    - 2. American Indian: The Legend of Scarface, afc2016057_dc481; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 3. Germany: Grimm, Musicians of Bremen, afc2016057_dc482; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 4. Denmark: Princess and the Pea, 5 Peas in a Pod, Thumbelina, afc2016057_dc483; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 5. Vietnam: Princess of Mt. Nam Nhu, afc2016057_dc484; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 6. Korea: Man Who Planted Onions, Silver Spoon, Stony Bag, Kim So-Ur, afc2016057_dc485; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 8. Bible: Legends of Noah, afc2016057_dc486; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 11. USA: The Way to Listen, afc2016057_dc487; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 12: Jewish: Number Our Days, afc2016057_dc488; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 15. USA: The Jazz Man, afc2016057_dc489; Harold Mabern; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 16. Thailand: Golden Swans, No Such Thing as a Secret, Emerald Buddha, afc2016057_dc490; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 17. Denmark: The Tinder Box, The Princess and the Pea, afc2016057_dc491; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 18. Denmark: The Silver Shilling, Princess Who Believed What She Heard, afc2016057_dc492; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 20. Yiddish: The Fools of Chelm, afc2016057_dc493; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 23. USA: The Boy, The Rat and the Butterfly, afc2016057_dc494; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 24. Denmark: The Shadow, afc2016057_dc495; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 25. American Indian: Finding the Center, afc2016057_dc496; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 27. Ireland: The Tinker of Tamlacht, afc2016057_dc497; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 29. Japan: Sea of Gold, Chio and Golo, New Year's Hats, afc2016057_dc498; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 31. Ireland: Wee Red Man, afc2016057_dc499; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 32. USA: A Certain Small Shepard, afc2016057_dc500; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 33. Turkey: Keloglan and the Magician, Keloglan and the Lucky Exchanges, afc2016057_dc501; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 34. Siberia: The Kaha Bird, afc2016057_dc502; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 35. Mexico: Birds of the Mayas, afc2016057_dc503; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 37. India: Beetle and Drop of Honey, afc2016057_dc504; With Tabla drum; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 38. Yiddish: Goldie the Dollmaker, afc2016057_dc505; With music; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 41. Haiti: Singing Bone, Put that Man to Bed, Erzulie, I'm Tipingee, Owl, afc2016057_dc506; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 42. Yiddish: Two Piano Tuners, afc2016057_dc507; With music; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 43. England: Elsie Piddock Skips in Her Sleep, afc2016057_dc508; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 44. Mexico: Boy Who Could Do Everything, afc2016057_dc509; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 47. France: The Devil's Bridge, Come Again in the Spring, afc2016057_dc510; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 48. USA: The Boy Who Sang Pictures, afc2016057_dc511; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 50. Wales: Pwyll, afc2016057_dc512; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 51. Tibet: The Rain Maker, afc2016057_dc513; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 53. USA: Bobby Shafto, John Henry, afc2016057_dc514; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 54. Jewish: A Tale of Kings, Part I, Yenne Velt, afc2016057_dc515; With music; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 62. USA: Elephant, Smash Small, Cars, afc2016057_dc516; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 63. Germany: The Fisherman and His Wife, afc2016057_dc517; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 64. French Canadian: Golden Phoenix, afc2016057_dc518; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 66. Haiti: Magic Orange Tree, afc2016057_dc519; With Shirley Keller; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 66. Haiti: Magic Orange Tree, Part 2, afc2016057_dc520; With Shirley Keller; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 67. England/Vietnam: First Snow, afc2016057_dc521; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 68. USA: Family Scrapbook, afc2016057_dc522; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 69. Sea Stories, afc2016057_dc523; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 70. The Fun Show: Mr. Gumpy, Man Whose Mother Was a Pirate, Pirate Boy, Little Woman Who Wanted Nurse, Val Teal, afc2016057_dc524; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 71. Mrs. Piggie Wiggle by Betty MacDonald, afc2016057_dc525; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 72. B'rer Rabbit, afc2016057_dc526; 2 sound files (WAV)
    - 73. Troll Ride, afc2016057_dc527; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 74. When Whale Came by Jim Young, afc2016057_dc528; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 75. England: Hungry Goblin, afc2016057_dc529; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 76. China: Story of Ming Y, afc2016057_dc530; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 77. America: Post Office Cat, afc2016057_dc531; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 78. Persia: Drop of Water, Precious Pearl, afc2016057_dc532; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 79. Eleanor Fargeau: Oranges and Lemons, The Herb of Fear, afc2016057_dc533; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 80. Grimm: Giant and Tailor, afc2016057_dc534; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 81. Kipling: The Curiosity Book, afc2016057_dc535; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 82. Haiti: Magic Orange Tree, One My Darling, The Forbidden Apple, Last Tiger in Haiti, Bye-Bye, afc2016057_dc536; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 83. Haiti: Magic Orange Tree, Horse and Toad, Singing Bone, Put That Man to Bed, afc2016057_dc537; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 84. Haiti: Magic Orange Tree, Hairs from Beard of Devil, Donkeys, Cat's Baptism, Monkey who Asked for Misery, Papa God and General Death, afc2016057_dc538; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 85. Haiti: Magic Orange Tree, Two Donkeys, Owl, afc2016057_dc539; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 86. USA: Charleston Ghosts, afc2016057_dc540; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 87. Hasidic, afc2016057_dc541; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 88. IB Singer: Fearsome Inn, afc2016057_dc542; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 89. Hasidic: Seer of Lublin, afc2016057_dc543; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 91. The Golden Treasure, afc2016057_dc544; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 92. England: Beatrix Potter, afc2016057_dc545; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 93. The Widow's Son, afc2016057_dc546; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 94. The Violin, afc2016057_dc547; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 95. Hawaii, afc2016057_dc548; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 96. England, afc2016057_dc549; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 97. Mystic: After His Death, Metamorphoses, Fastest Balaika, afc2016057_dc550; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 98. [Unlabeled], afc2016057_dc202; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 99. Africa, afc2016057_dc552; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 100. USA?, afc2016057_dc553; 1 sound file (WAV)
    - 101. USA, afc2016057_dc554; 1 sound file (WAV)